<resources>
    <!-- App name -->
    <string name="app_name">Wellbees</string>

    <!-- About Screen -->
    <string name="about_title">Hakkında</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">WELLBEES PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY</string>

    <!-- Privacy Policy Content -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_intro">This is the Privacy and Cookies Policy for the Wellbees Application (the \"App\"). The App is operated by or on behalf of Actifit Spor ve Sağlık Hizmetleri Sanayi ve Ticaret Anonim Şirketi, (\'we\', \'us\', \'our\' or \"Actifit\").\n\nThis policy sets out how we collect and use your personal data in connection with the provision of our services to you through the App. This policy covers:\n\n• Information we collect about you and how we use it\n• Cookies and other technologies\n• Communications\n• Who we give your information to\n• Where we store and transfer your information\n• Child safety\n• How we protect your information\n• How long we keep your information\n• Your rights\n• Changes to this policy\n• Contacting us\n\nWe are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we may treat it.\n\nBy accepting our services and using the App, you acknowledge you have read and understood this privacy policy.\n\nFor the purposes of UK and European Economic Area data protection law, (the \"Data Protection Law\") the data controller is: Actifit Spor ve Sağlık Hizmetleri Sanayi ve Ticaret Limited Şirketi with its headquarters at Levent Mahallesi Fulyalı Sokak No:7 Beşiktaş, İstanbul.</string>

    <string name="information_collected_title">INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT YOU AND HOW WE USE IT</string>

    <string name="information_collected_content">The App will collect and process the following personal data from you:\n\nInformation you give us as an App user\nThis is information you enter directly when you interact with the App. This includes where you:\n\n• Register to create an account with us.\n• Log diary notes about your health and wellbeing.\n• Book expert sessions.\n• Attend virtual events.\n• Collect WellPoints (if your employer has enabled this feature).\n• Participate in surveys or research.\n• Ask questions or submit a query.\n\nThis is information about you that you record by filling in forms and using different App features. It includes information to:\n\nRegister to create an account with us: you will need to set up an account with us in order to use the App. We ask for\nIdentity information: your name, username and chosen password\nContact information: your email address.\n\nThis is so we can create an account in your name, identify you as the account holder when you log in and use the App and contact you where appropriate with specific administrative service messages about your account.\n\nRecord information about yourself: you can enter profile details about yourself.\nProfile information: (e.g. your date of birth, your residing location, your gender, height, weight and your wellbeing interests).\nJob information: (e.g. your employer\'s name, your department, job title, company location).\n\nLog diary notes: about your daily health and wellbeing and activity or experiences including your mood.\nHealth information: about your physical and mental health and wellbeing, including details about your mood, sleep, activity, nutrition or water intake.\n\nBook expert sessions: if you would like to partake in a therapy or nutrition session, we ask for:\nIdentity information, contact information and health information in connection with booking your session. The expert will then contact you via a videocall via the platform. We also keep a record of the number of sessions that you have taken, and with which experts you have spoken.\n\nAttend a virtual event: if you choose to attend a virtual event we ask for:\nIdentity information and contact information so you can book the event. We also keep a record of the events that you attend.\n\nInteract with other users or experts: we use your identity information to enable you to interact with other users or experts in the App.\n\nTrack your WellPoints: if your employer has enabled this feature, we ask for:\nIdentity information, details about events attended, and other health information that you input or via health app integrations (see information we collect from integrated apps below) such as how much water you have drank or activities undertaken. This is used to issue WellPoints, which can be redeemed against discount codes and coupons, expert sessions, and other items decided by your employer.\n\nParticipate in a survey or research: if you choose to participate in a survey or research,\nIdentity information, and health information in connection with sharing your experiences.\n\nAsk questions: if you submit a query regarding the App. We will use the details you provide to investigate and respond.\nIdentity information: in connection with responding to any questions or enquiries you raise with us.\n\nInformation you give if you are an expert: we will collect information about your identity, qualifications and other information about your education and work history, contact information, CVS and payment information to sign you up as an expert and enable you to book sessions with clients.\n\nInformation we collect about you from your use the App: we will automatically collect usage information from you each time you visit the App. This includes:\nTechnical information.\nInformation about your engagement with the App.\nInformation we collect from integrated apps: if you choose to enable us access to select other health apps, we can integrate health data from these apps such as step count, activity levels, nutrition or sleep tracking information.\n\nTechnical information: we collect the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the Internet, your device make and model and identifiers, App version, browser type (e.g. Apple Safari or Google Chrome) and operating system version. We also receive information about the content of a request as well as the time zone setting, date and http status code associated with the request.\n\nInformation about your engagement with the App: may include the App session data traffic, including date and time, content viewed or searched for, click details to see the types of club/challenge/event/content/program that you click on, content load response times, download errors, length of session. This is so that we can understand how the App is used and in the case of your searches, display to you ranked feedback, editorial content, summary reports and content relevant to your search terms. We also collect information about the number of challenges you have participated in, events attended and your interactions with other users or experts in the App.\n\nInformation we collect from integrated apps: if you choose to enable us access to select other apps, we can integrate health data from these apps such as step count, activity levels, nutrition or sleep tracking information. You can select which apps you would like to integrate with the App, and can turn off the integration at any time.\n\nYou can see a full list of the types of data we process, the purpose for which we process it and the lawful basis on which it is processed end of the document.</string>

    <string name="cookies_title">COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES</string>

    <string name="cookies_content">The App uses cookies and/or other similar technologies to collect and store certain information. These typically involve pieces of information or code transferred to or accessed from your mobile device to store and sometimes track information about you. Cookies and similar technologies enable you to be remembered when using that device to interact with online services and can be used to manage a range of features and content as well as storing searches and presenting personalised content.\n\nThe App uses cookies and similar technologies to distinguish you from other users of the App. This helps us to provide you with a personalised experience when you navigate the App and also allows us to improve our content and services.\n\nMost browsers automatically accept cookies and similar technologies, but if you prefer, you can change your device privacy settings to enable you to do this. We also give you information about how to disable cookies below. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our App if you do so.\n\nA number of cookies and similar technologies we use last only for the duration of your App session and expire when you exit the App. Others are used to remember you when you return to the App and will last for longer.\n\nWe use these cookies and other technologies on the basis our legitimate interests (where such cookies are strictly necessary for the operation of the App (and we have considered that these are not overridden by your rights),or otherwise where you have consented to their use.\n\nWe may use the following types of cookies:\n\n• Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our App and under our terms with you. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into your account and manage your session.\n• Functional cookies. These enable us, subject to your choices and preferences, to personalise the look or appearance of certain content on the App,\n• Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognise and count the number users and to see how they engage with our App content and features. This helps us to identify, ways of improving our App, for example by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.\n\nSponsored promotional content that appears within the app is generated by the content you view or inputted symptom or search terms you use and not through the use of third-party advertising cookies. For example, an article or search relevant to dry skin may be matched with sponsored content for a specific moisturising cream product.\n\nThe effect of disabling cookies depends on which cookies you disable but, in general, the Platform may not operate properly if all cookies are switched off.\n\nIf you want to disable cookies and equivalent technology used on the App, you can change your device privacy settings to reject cookies.\n\nWhere you have not set your permissions, we may also separately prompt you regarding our use of cookies and similar technologies through the App.</string>

    <string name="communications_title">COMMUNICATIONS</string>

    <string name="communications_content">Where permitted in our legitimate interest we may communicate specific administrative service messages about your account. We may also where permitted in our legitimate interest or with your prior consent where required by Data Protection Law, use your personal information for analysis or to communicate messages relevant to promoting a better user experience of the App, or to let you know about our other products and services.\n\nYou can withdraw your consent, where provided, to our promotional communications at any time by selecting the unsubscribe link at the end of our communication to you or by contacting us at: info@wellbees.co</string>

    <string name="who_we_give_info_title">WHO WE GIVE YOUR INFORMATION TO</string>

    <string name="who_we_give_info_content">We may make personal Information available to:\n\n• Select experts to enable you to book an expert session (e.g. a videocall with a therapist, dietician or nutritionist).\n• A member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, who support our processing of personal data under this policy. To see a full list of such companies please click here. If any of these parties are using your information for their own purpose, we will only transfer the information to them for that purpose with your prior consent.\n• Your employer, but only in aggregate form about their workplace as a whole so they will never be able to identify you. If an expert has reason to believe that you intend to harm yourself, we may share this with the authorities for your safety.\n• Selected third parties.\n\nOur selected third parties may include:\n\nOrganisations who process your personal data on our behalf and in accordance with our instructions and the Data Protection Law. This includes in supporting the services we offer through the App in particular those providing data hosting services, providing fulfilment services, distributing any communications we send, facilitating feedback on our services and providing IT App support and development services from time to time. These organisations (which may include third party suppliers, agents, sub-contractors and/or other companies in our group) will only access your information to the extent necessary to perform their support functions.\n\nOur analytics provider who assists us in the improvement and optimisation of the App and subject to the cookie section of this policy (this will not identify you as an individual).\n\nWe will share data with your employer about the general wellbeing of their workforce, but we will only do this on an aggregate basis so they will not be able to identify you from any of the data.\n\nWe may disclose your personal information to third parties:\n\nIn the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets subject to the terms of this privacy policy.\n\nIf Actifit or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.\n\nIf we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of supply terms and other agreements with you; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Actifit our end users, or others. This includes:\nsharing information with competent national or regional regulatory authorities where we are obliged to assess, and report information; or\nexchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and to prevent cybercrime.</string>

    <string name="where_we_store_title">WHERE WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION</string>

    <string name="where_we_store_content">The information that we collect is hosted on secure servers located within the EEA and Turkey and, may specifically be hosted and or processed on secure servers in the context of the country you reside and where the App is provided, (where required by law).\n\nTo the extent any access your personal information or transfer of such information is anticipated outside the UK or EEA in the context of supporting the operation of the services provided through the App, we will take steps to ensure that your data is subject to appropriate safeguards, such as relying on a recognised legal adequacy finding or mechanism, and that it is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.\n\nWe may transfer your personal information outside the UK and EEA to Turkey:\n\n• In order support the operation of the services provided by the App.\n• Where we are legally required to do so.\n• In order to facilitate the operation of our group of businesses, where it is in our legitimate interests and we have concluded these are not overridden by your rights.\n\nWhere we transfer your personal information to a jurisdiction not subject to a relevant legal transfer adequacy finding, we will take steps to ensure an appropriate legal adequacy safeguard is in place which usually means, use of specific approved contracts that rely upon standard contractual clauses (\"SCCs\") for the protection of personal data.\n\nFor further information on transfers outside of the UK and EEA and/or the specific safeguard methods adopted, please contact info@wellbees.co</string>

    <string name="child_safety_title">CHILD SAFETY</string>

    <string name="child_safety_content">Protecting the safety of children when they use the Internet and online services is important to us. The App is intended for use only by persons who are at least 18 years of age. By using the App you confirm to us that you meet this requirement.</string>

    <string name="data_protection_title">HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION</string>

    <string name="data_protection_content">All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of the App, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.\n\nUnfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the App; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.\n\nOur App may, from time to time, contain links to external sites. Where you engage with sponsored content on the App that will take you to a third party site we will notify you that you are about to leave the App. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.\n\nThe App does not use personal data to make automated decisions in any way that has any legal effect or significantly affect upon you.</string>

    <string name="data_retention_title">HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION</string>

    <string name="data_retention_content">We retain personal data for as long as you use the App and have an account with us. We may also retain aggregate information for research purposes and to help us develop and improve our products and services. You cannot be identified from aggregate information retained or used for these purposes.</string>

    <string name="user_rights_title">YOUR RIGHTS</string>

    <string name="user_rights_content">You have the right under certain circumstances:\n\n• to be provided with a copy of your personal data held by us;\n• to request the rectification or erasure of your personal data held by us;\n• to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data (while we verify or investigate your concerns with this information, for example);\n• to object to the further processing of your personal data,\n• to request that your provided personal data be moved to a third party,\n• not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling, which produces legal effects concerning you or that similarly significantly affect you (note, as stated above, this App does not use personal data to make such automated decisions).\n\nYou may opt out at any time from allowing further access by us to your location data by altering the privacy settings of your device. You can also stop all information collection by un-installing the App. You may use the standard un-install processes as may be available for your mobile device.\n\nYour right to withdraw consent: where the processing of your personal information by us is based on consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent without detriment at any time by contacting us as set out below.\n\nWhere we receive a request to exercise one of the above rights, we will normally respond within one month. This may be extended by up to two further months in cases where requests are complex or numerous and where such an extension is permitted by Data Protection Law. Where that is the case we will inform you within one month of any extension and the reason for this.\n\nYou can also exercise the rights listed above at any time by contacting us at info@actifit.com.tr\n\nIf your request or concern is not satisfactorily resolved by us, you may approach your local data protection authority, (see http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.html ). The Information Commissioner is the supervisory authority in the UK and can provide further information about your rights and our obligations in relation to your personal data, as well as deal with any complaints that you have about our processing of your personal data.</string>

    <string name="policy_changes_title">CHANGES TO THIS POLICY</string>

    <string name="policy_changes_content">Any changes we make to our privacy policy in future will be posted on this page and, in relation to substantive changes, will be notified to you by e-mail. This policy was last updated in June 2021.</string>

    <string name="contact_title">CONTACT US</string>

    <string name="contact_content">Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed for the attention of Kerem Gonulkirmaz, CTO of Wellbees.\n\nEmail: info@wellbees.co\nPost: Levent Mahallesi Fulyalı Sokak No:7 Beşiktaş, İstanbul</string>

    <string name="data_table_title">PURPOSE AND LAWFUL BASIS FOR PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA</string>

    <string name="data_table_intro">This table sets out:\n\n• What personal data we process\n• What we use that data for\n• The lawful basis for the processing\n\nIt forms part of our privacy policy which you should also read.</string>

    <!-- Table Headers -->
    <string name="table_header_purpose">Purpose/Activity</string>
    <string name="table_header_type">Type of data</string>
    <string name="table_header_lawful">Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest</string>

    <!-- Table Row 1 -->
    <string name="table_row1_purpose">To register you as a new user of the App.</string>
    <string name="table_row1_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact</string>
    <string name="table_row1_lawful">(a) Performance of our terms with you.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 2 -->
    <string name="table_row2_purpose">If you are an expert, to perform our agreement with you and book sessions with clients.</string>
    <string name="table_row2_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact</string>
    <string name="table_row2_lawful">(a) Performance of our terms with you.\n(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to manage expert sessions).</string>

    <!-- Table Row 3 -->
    <string name="table_row3_purpose">To manage our relationship with you which will include:\n(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy\n(b) Responding to your questions and queries</string>
    <string name="table_row3_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact</string>
    <string name="table_row3_lawful">(a) Performance of our terms with you.\n(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.\n(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how users engage with the App and our services).</string>

    <!-- Table Row 4 -->
    <string name="table_row4_purpose">To provide you with health tips and wellness resources and health tracking.</string>
    <string name="table_row4_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Health</string>
    <string name="table_row4_lawful">(a) Performance of our terms with you.\n(b) Explicit consent.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 5 -->
    <string name="table_row5_purpose">To enable you to book expert sessions.</string>
    <string name="table_row5_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact\n(c) Health</string>
    <string name="table_row5_lawful">(a) Explicit consent.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 6 -->
    <string name="table_row6_purpose">To administer WellPoints.</string>
    <string name="table_row6_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Health</string>
    <string name="table_row6_lawful">(a) Performance of our terms with you.\n(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (being the effective management of our services).</string>

    <!-- Table Row 7 -->
    <string name="table_row7_purpose">To enable you to partake in a survey, research or attend an event.</string>
    <string name="table_row7_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact\n(c) Health\n(d) Usage</string>
    <string name="table_row7_lawful">(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how users engage with our services, to develop them and grow our business).\n(b) Research purposes. Defining and progressing research priorities.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 8 -->
    <string name="table_row8_purpose">To administer and protect our business and this App (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data).</string>
    <string name="table_row8_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact\n(c) Technical</string>
    <string name="table_row8_lawful">(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganisation or group restructuring exercise).\n(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 9 -->
    <string name="table_row9_purpose">To a) deliver relevant content to you;\nb) communicate App engagement information by email</string>
    <string name="table_row9_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Contact\n(c) Usage\n(d) Technical</string>
    <string name="table_row9_lawful">(a)Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how users engage with our services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our business strategy).\nb) Consent where communication constitutes marketing.</string>

    <!-- Table Row 10 -->
    <string name="table_row10_purpose">To use data analytics, crash reporting and push messaging and linking tools to improve our website, products/services.</string>
    <string name="table_row10_type">(a) Technical\n(b) Usage</string>
    <string name="table_row10_lawful">(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of users for our services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our business strategy).\nb) Consent (where applicable to the particular method of collection (e.g. cookies and similar technologies).</string>

    <!-- Table Row 11 -->
    <string name="table_row11_purpose">De-identification of data to understand at an aggregated level, health trends, identify research priorities and to improve our services.</string>
    <string name="table_row11_type">(a) Identity\n(b) Health</string>
    <string name="table_row11_lawful">(a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to inform our services and wider business strategy).\nb) Consent.</string>
</resources>