<resources>
    <!-- Terms of Service -->
    <string name="terms_title">Hizmet Kullanım Koşulları</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_title">Terms of Use</string>

    <!-- Introduction -->
    <string name="terms_introduction_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="terms_introduction_content">These terms and conditions of use apply to your access to the [Wellbees] platform (Platform). The Platform is operated by or on behalf of Actifit Spor Sağlık Hizmetleri San Tic AŞ trading as Wellbees (we, us and our).\n\nThe Wellbees Platform allows you to access sustainable wellbeing services and activities. Your employer (Employer) has entered into an agreement with us to allow us to provide you, as their employee, with access to the Platform.\n\nYour use of the Platform will be subject to (a) you remaining an employee of your Employer; and (b) these terms and conditions. By using the Platform you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions.\n\nWe reserve the right to change these terms and conditions from time to time by changing them on the Platform. These terms and conditions were last updated on May 2025.</string>

    <!-- Access to Platform -->
    <string name="terms_access_title">Access to the Platform</string>
    <string name="terms_access_content">The Platform is intended for use by persons who are at least 18 years of age and are an employer of the Employer.\n\nTo access the Platform you may be required to register with us. You must ensure that any registration details you provide are accurate. You must keep your log-on IP (such as a username and password or other identifier) as confidential and must not reveal it to anyone else. You are responsible for all activities that occur under your log-on ID and must notify us and your Employer immediately of any unauthorised use or other security breach of which you become aware.\n\nWe reserve the right to disable any log-on ID, at any time, if: (a) in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms and conditions; (b) any details you provide for the purposes of registering as a user prove to be false; or (c) you cease to be an employee of the Employer.\n\nWe reserve the right to inform your Employer, including providing relevant information as to reason, should we decide that we will disable your log-on ID due to you being in breach of these terms of use.\n\nWe cannot guarantee the continuous, uninterrupted or error-free operability of the Platform. There may be times when certain features, parts or content of the Platform, or the entire Platform, become unavailable (whether on a scheduled or unscheduled basis) or are modified, suspended or withdrawn by us, in our sole discretion, without notice to you. You agree that we will not be liable to you or to any third party for any unavailability, modification, suspension or withdrawal of the Platform, or any features, parts or content of the Platform.</string>

    <!-- What you are allowed to do -->
    <string name="terms_allowed_title">What you are allowed to do</string>
    <string name="terms_allowed_content">You may only use the Platform for non-commercial use and only in accordance with these terms and conditions. You may retrieve and display content from the Platform on a computer screen, print and copy individual pages and, subject to the next section, store such pages in electronic form. Additional terms may also apply to certain features, parts or content of the Platform and, where they apply, will be displayed on-screen or accessible via a link.</string>

    <!-- What you are not allowed to do -->
    <string name="terms_not_allowed_title">What you are not allowed to do</string>
    <string name="terms_not_allowed_content">Except to the extent expressly set out in these terms and conditions, you are not allowed to:\n\n\'scrape\' content or store content of the Platform on a server or other storage device connected to a network or create an electronic database by systematically downloading and storing all of the content of the Platform;\n\nremove or change any content of the Platform or attempt to circumvent security or interfere with the proper working of the Platform or the servers on which it is hosted; or\n\ncreate links to the Platform from any other webPlatform, without our prior written consent.\n\nYou must only use the Platform and any services or activities available through the Platform for lawful purposes (complying with all applicable laws and regulations), in a responsible manner, and not in a way that might damage our and/or your Employer\'s name or reputation or that of any of our and/or your Employer\'s affiliates.\n\nAll rights granted to you under these terms and conditions will terminate immediately in the event that you are in breach of any of them.</string>

    <!-- Intellectual Property Rights -->
    <string name="terms_ip_title">Intellectual property rights</string>
    <string name="terms_ip_content">All intellectual property rights in any content of the Platform (including text, graphics, software, photographs and other images, videos, sound, trade marks and logos) are owned by us or our licensors. Except as expressly set out here, nothing in these terms and conditions gives you any rights in respect of any intellectual property owned by us or our licensors and you acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by downloading content from the Platform. In the event you print off, copy or store pages from the Platform (only as permitted by these terms and conditions), you must ensure that any copyright, trade mark or other intellectual property right notices contained in the original content are reproduced.</string>

    <!-- Content -->
    <string name="terms_content_title">Content</string>
    <string name="terms_content_content">We may change the format and content of the Platform from time to time. You agree that your use of the Platform is on an \'as is\' and \'as available\' basis and at your sole risk.\n\nWhilst we try to make sure that all information contained on the Platform (other than any user-generated content) is correct, it is not intended to amount to authority or advice on which reliance should be placed. You should check with us or the relevant information source before acting on any such information.\n\nWe make or give no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness, currency, correctness, reliability, integrity, quality, fitness for purpose or originality of any content of the Platform and, to the fullest extent permitted by law, all implied warranties, conditions or other terms of any kind are hereby excluded and we accept no liability for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of you or anyone else using the Platform or relying on any of its content.\n\nWe cannot and do not guarantee that any content of the Platform will be free from viruses and/or other code that may have contaminating or destructive elements. It is your responsibility to implement appropriate IT security safeguards (including anti-virus and other security checks) to satisfy your particular requirements as to the safety and reliability of content.</string>

    <!-- Personal Information -->
    <string name="terms_personal_info_title">Your personal information</string>
    <string name="terms_personal_info_content">Use of your personal information submitted to or via the Platform is governed by our Privacy Policy.</string>

    <!-- User Content -->
    <string name="terms_user_content_title">User content</string>
    <string name="terms_user_content_content">If The Platform may, from time to time, allow you to upload user-generated content and may also allow you to communicate that content, either to selected recipients or in public areas, such as comments pages, message boards, and/or news groups (collectively User Content Areas). We do not control the material submitted to User Content Areas (collectively User Submissions), nor are User Content Areas actively moderated. You are solely responsible for the content of your User Submissions as submitted by you and acknowledge that all User Submissions express the views of their respective authors, and not our views.\n\nIf you participate in any User Content Areas, you must keep all User Submissions relevant to the purpose of the User Content Area and the nature of any topic.\n\nUser Submissions must not:\n\ncontain, transmit, distribute, link to or otherwise make available, or advertise or promote any content that infringes any intellectual property rights or data protection, privacy or other rights of any other person, is defamatory or in breach of any contractual duty or any obligation of confidence, is obscene, sexually explicit, threatening, abusive, harassing, inciteful of violence or hatred, blasphemous, discriminatory (on any ground), liable to cause anxiety, alarm or embarrassment, knowingly false or misleading, or that does not comply with all applicable laws and regulations or is otherwise objectionable (\"Prohibited Content\");\n\nimpersonate any person or entity or otherwise misrepresent your relationship with any person or entity;\n\ncontain, transmit or distribute any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising, marketing or promotional material or other form of solicitation (spam); or\n\ntransmit or distribute any virus and/or other code that has contaminating or destructive elements.\n\nYou agree that, by submitting any User Submission, you grant us and our affiliates a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free and fully sub-licensable right and licence to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, perform and display such User Submission (in whole or part) and/or to incorporate it in other works in any form, media or technology, and you waive any moral rights you may have in, or to be identified as the author, of such User Submission.\n\nWhilst we do not pre-screen User Submissions, we reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to delete, edit or modify any User Submission submitted by you and/or to close any topic, at any time without notice to you.\n\nComplaints about the content of any User Submission must be sent to support@wellbees.co and must contain details of the specific User Submission giving rise to the complaint.</string>

    <!-- Third Party Services -->
    <string name="terms_third_party_title">Third Party Services</string>
    <string name="terms_third_party_content">The Platform may allow you to access certain wellbeing services provided by third parties. We are not responsible for these services or for anything that does or does not happen in the provision of services by third parties. We have no liability for the content of these services or any of the services provided by these service providers. Further we do not guarantee that they will be always available or that you will satisfy any participation criteria.</string>

    <!-- General -->
    <string name="terms_general_title">General</string>
    <string name="terms_general_content">Nothing in these terms and conditions shall limit or exclude our liability to you:\n\nfor death or personal injury caused by our negligence;\n\nfor fraudulent misrepresentation; or\n\nfor any other liability that, by law, may not be limited or excluded.\n\nThese terms and conditions shall be governed by English law. You agree that any dispute between you and us regarding these terms and conditions or the Platform will only be dealt with by the English courts.</string>

    <!-- Contact -->
    <string name="terms_contact_title">Contacting us</string>
    <string name="terms_contact_content">Please submit any questions you have about these terms and conditions or any problems concerning the Platform by email to support@wellbees.co.</string>
</resources>